But again, people and others
Animals cannot get sick from the virus.
But if
The disease cannot be prevented from spreading within Sweden
would it cause any damage among tame pigs and wild boar
And it would be very expensive to fight.
Infected animals exhibit a variety of symptoms
such as high fever, loss of appetite.
Signs of weakness in the body.
For example, the animal may have difficulty standing up.
Vomiting, diarrhea, red or bluish skin,
Most often around the throne and ears.
The course of the disease may vary but in many cases lead
That to death within about 5 to 10 days.
The disease was first discovered among tame pigs
in Kenya in the early 1900s.
For the fewer pigs found in the area
The greater the ability to limit and fight the infection.
At present, there is no effective vaccine against African swine fever.
Research is ongoing to develop one,
But so far, no successful solution has been found.
The best way to prevent dissemination is through strict hygiene actions,
monitoring and control of animal transport.
I hope you have learned a little more about what African swine plague is for something.
Feel free to subscribe to my channel.
And as always, thank you for watching!